[{"answer": "It was definitely very sad.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "What was your feeling today as you sat in the courtroom watching the events?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "When you saw the shooter up close, as you did today, did it shock you even more that he was able to arm himself in the horrifying manner that he did?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, we did it as a way to bring attention to the fact that we have all of these foreigners and the Russian government, the official Chinese government, now said political power goes out the barrel of a gun.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Why do you want to deport me?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Yes, I am finished.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Are you finished?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "There were about 11,458, and about 70 percent of those were gang related.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "How many great white sharks --", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "How many gun murders were there in Britain last year?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "kill people every year but they're scared to swim?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "A very low amount.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "How many gun murders were there in Britain?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "That was only a few hundred.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "How many, do you know?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "I actually -- actually brought statistics.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "How many gun murders?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Answer this question.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Why don't you go back and face the charges with the hacking scandal?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "How --", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Why did you get fired from \"The Daily Mirror\" for putting that fag stories?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "You know the answer?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Yes, England wants to ban knives now because tens of thousands are getting stabbed.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Do you understand the difference in 11,000 and 35?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Do you understand --", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Do you understand the difference?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "They know your script.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "-- and 11,000?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "ONES: An M-4 AR-15 variant.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Let me ask you one question, which weapon was predominantly used in the Aurora movie theater shooting?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Now I believe that there were others --", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Do you know that?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "I understand that people who were mentally ill on all the --", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "Do you know which weapon was used in the Oregon shopping mall mass shooting recently?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Listen.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Do you know what the weapon used was?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Alex.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Do you have a body guard?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "I don't have a body guard.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Why do you have body guards?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Why does Dianne Feinstein --", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Let me ask you this question?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Don't be (INAUDIBLE) over me.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "-- to try and take Mr. And Mrs. America's guns?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "I have already gone over that.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "What was the weapon used at Sandy Hook?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "It's a 223 M-4.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "What was the weapon?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Why -- Alex. I don't --", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Why is the government (INAUDIBLE) against this?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Alex.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "What about \"Fast and Furious\"?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Calm down.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Why did our government ship guns to Mexico?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Let's have a debate.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "To blame the Second Amendment?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "Alex, I get accused --", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "A false flag?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "I get accused --", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "To blame the Second Amendment?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Alex. Alex. I get accused when I get you guys on of talking over you, of being rude.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Why they blow up buildings down the street here in New York?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "All right?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Go commit suicide by killing a bunch of kids and here's the gun to use --", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "Alex, why do people need them?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "They need them to protect us from the number one killer in history.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Why do people need them?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Statistically, where there's mo more guns, there's lower crime.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "-- therefore have an AR-15 if they want one?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Stick to the topic.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Is they're half your sponsors?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "I absolutely know.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Who do you believe was behind 9/11?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I have the proof.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Yes, but who do you believe was behind it?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "They announced they blew up the towers on CBS Radio.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Who, Alex?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Criminal elements of the military and industrial complex, the same ones that staged (INAUDIBLE), the same ones that staged operation --", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "The American government?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "I mean that even mainstream news reported that the hijackers were ordered to be allowed into the United States.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Alex. Alex. Do you mean that President Bush and his administration were behind 9/11?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "The government -- Hitler fired bombs and turned rash tag, Piers.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "But is that what you believe?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "I probably own more than 50 firearms.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "How many guns do you own?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "I don't think you're right about that.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "What is brave about wanting to stop 20 more children getting murders?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "ERSHOWITZ: Because we think it's their issue.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Explain to me why you believe that the answer to these gun massacres is to have a lot more guns.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "How are you doing, Piers?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "We don't pick them off the streets.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "Why are on Earth do you think these patrolmen, as you put it, who you have taken of the streets and given a bit of training to, could do any better?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "What about this old quaint idea, what about taking guns off the streets rather than flooding the streets with more guns?", "qSentId": 729}, {"answer": "It was disheartening, I think, you know, I think just to see the anger there.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 816, "question": "What did you feel?", "qSentId": 815}, {"answer": "During the aftermath of Obamacare, when there were -- the president was being held in effigy and these kinds of threatening comments of people like the man you just had on were blocking members of Congress from being able to go and vote, you may recall, of that.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 826, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 825}, {"answer": "ENNEDY: Well, as I said, I think that the lack of discourse -- so that that is really what's offensive in our country, where we should be able to debate our problems without impugning the integrity of the people who have positions.", "docId": "130107pmt", "aSentId": 864, "question": "Are you surprised that following the assassinations of John F. Kennedy and of Bobby Kennedy that we are in a position in America now where these kind of lawless mass shootings are happening with regularity and no one is doing much about it?", "qSentId": 863}]